import 'package:quiz_app_tutorial/models/question.dart';

const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. If he had attended the party, he ______ me',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) would have seen',
      'b) will',
      'c) would see',
      'd) will see',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. Whenever you buy an article, insist ______ being given the receipt',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) on',
      'b) at',
      'c) in',
      'd) to',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. The most rescent shootout resulted _____ the death of many',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) into',
      'b) in',
      'c) to',
      'd) at',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. If he _____ the truth, I would have forgiven him.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) had told',
      'b) had',
      'c) told',
      'd) might told',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. I am the one who ____ the fowl.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) catch',
      'b) catched',
      'c) cought',
      'd) had catched',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '6. Mecury is the smallest planet _______ our solar system?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) of',
      'b) at',
      'c) inside',
      'd) in',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. ______ wrote the play Romeo and Juliet?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Who',
      'b) Whom',
      'c) Whos',
      'd) Did who',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. In my hands _____ some good mellons',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) is',
      'b) are',
      'c) was',
      "d) wasn't",
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '9. There are _______ genders.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) about 41',
      'b) 10',
      'c) 5',
      'd) exactly 2',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '10. They say "Practice makes _______".',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Partial',
      'b) Personal',
      'c) Perfect',
      'd) Punctual',
    ],
  ),
];
